[{"answer": "Well, everyone that we've been speaking to, Wolf, and I literally just landed here a few hours ago, is incredibly distraught over what took place.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "What's the scene like there?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "Well, it is 3:00 in the morning here, Wolf.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "What's going on right now?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, I just think his overall critique is the same which is there's been a lot of uncertainty and mixed messages being sent throughout the region.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "A deliberate shift?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Well, at the time his initial statement went out, we knew there have been --", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "But after the administration withdrew that statement, why did he have to double down the next morning after we knew that the American ambassador and three other Americans were killed?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "The -- the embassy in Cairo had reissued the statement via social networks.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "But why the next morning did he have to repeat it?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Wolf, he made a criticism about a statement that came out of the U.S. embassy in Cairo.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "And the question is, was that a mistake?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Yes, well, it's much more.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Does Mitt Romney support continuing more than $1 billion a year in military and economic assistance to Egypt?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "He believes that we should take a close look at conditioning that aid based on Egypt, the Egyptian government being a responsible player, responsible act in the region.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Does Mitt Romney think that should go on?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Well, this is politics.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Yes, and no direct response when the president says, you shoot first and aim later?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Well, Wolf, look, you know, you wish that for 24 hours or 48 hours, people wouldn't seize on politics, that there'd be a moment for prayer, reflection, strong action by the commander in chief, and America comes together, rather than looking at polling numbers and trying to seize an opportunity.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "You accept his explanation of why he initially criticized the Obama administration?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "I don't think there is a problem with arguing about national security.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "What's wrong with candidates arguing over national security?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Well, the president, I know, feels that Egypt is a partner.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "The president or the State Department?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "In -- well, not just in Iran, we had an ambassador killed in Kabul followed by the embassy in Islamabad being burned to the ground, followed by the takeover in Tehran.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "In Iran?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "What it should be doing is what they're starting to do now.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "So what should the administration in your opinion be doing?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Yes, but very restricted and very targeted.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Isn't that an act -- a decisive act?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Is the U.S. better off with these dictators gone or was it better off before?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "This is an important moment for Mitt Romney.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "How important is this for Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I think it is really quite unique.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Doug, how common is it for the challenger, the non-incumbent, the candidate, to be this aggressive in reacting to a foreign policy issue like Mitt Romney did this week?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "No, they are not expressing any regret.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Gloria, in your conversations with Romney sources, have they expressed any regret about the way Romney handled this?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Well, you know, Wolf, imagine if Barack Obama had not gotten Osama bin Laden and Gadhafi.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Is this likely to have a huge impact come November 6th?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "I understand Google's position and I understand why they did this, but they set themselves a terrible precedent, because we can not live in a society where anything that could offend anyone has to be taken down.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Jeff, what do you think about this?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "I think you should go ahead and show it or at least link to it on Youtube, because it is so patently ridiculous.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Jeff, what do you think about that decision?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "I am not sure he made a huge mistake, but I think a lot of the folks who work in this -- who work in that field, in both parties -- I'm pretty sure Rick is an exception to this -- thought it was a mistake to go out and make a statement before the facts were clear.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Did Mitt Romney make a big mistake when he called out the president over that Cairo embassy initial statement?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Ben just called it jumping out.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "You think it was necessarily a mistake, right?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "You use the bully pulpit.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Rick, how would he calm it down?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think that's certainly the fact that there -- there are riots around U.S. embassies in four countries, including in ones where Barack Obama reluctantly or very jubilantly supported the revolution, is a real foreign policy debate Republicans are trying to have.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Ben, are the Republicans having an impact in suggesting -- accusing the president of having a weak foreign policy?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Well, I think if you believe the polls, you would be worried.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "How worried are you right now that he's just not doing well?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120913pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Rick, if Romney would have said that, would there have been a lot more criticism, shall we say, for screwing up an answer?", "qSentId": 535}]